Hi everyone, this is EYA on EYA Censored
Supernatural Bible Changes on YouTube.
Today is a Friday,
April 10th, 2026.
I want to share with you my website,
bible-changes.com.
This is a great resource for anyone
who's wants to research what's happening
to our Bibles.
I put together so many resources to help
those of you who are searching out the
matter, who want to easy access to lists
of words or scripture verses that have
been altered,
this is the place, okay? Now, again,
this is bible-changes.com.
You can learn information about me. You
can look at my shop with a list of my
books that are available on Amazon on
the Bible Changes. You can also click
here for examples on the Bible Changes.
And I have
information here on the changes that we
see now in our Bibles with screenshots
from one of my King James Bibles you can
take a look at.
These are really great examples of the
types of changes that we are seeing in
our Bibles so obviously changed. We find
nonsense verses, grammar errors,
punctuation errors, emoticons, new
doctrine, new words, words omitted,
um new titles to different books of the
Bible,
um new doctrine, I think I mentioned
that, new people, and on and on it goes.
So many obvious, clear changes
that we are seeing to our Bibles. And
the Bibles are changing across the
board, across translations and across
languages.
And it's time to wake up in Jesus' name.
But this website, I think, provides so
many resources for you, the researcher,
to gather clear, concrete examples of
what's happening to our Bibles, and for
you to share with your
community, with your pastor, with your
friends, your family, your colleagues,
with strangers. Just get the word out
about what's happening to scripture.
This is the abomination of desolation
standing in the holy place. There is
zero doubt in my mind.
I've been studying this phenomena for
almost a decade.
And I've had my YouTube channel, I've
had several.
Um I've been on YouTube since 2016
searching out this matter.
And I am very passionate about it
because I understand
the enormity of what this means for
eternity because
the Bible is being has been already
turned into a book of fables.
And
this really is the strong delusion.
And these are lying signs and wonders,
and we were always told in the book of
Thessalonians,
Second Thessalonians,
that
in the end, there will be a great
falling away, that the Antichrist would
come with lying signs and wonders. Do
you remember that? We are seeing this
happen right now. And most of the church
is sadly and woefully asleep.
So, take a look at this. Anyway, lots of
resources here on
this website, but I really want to show
this to you first. Join the Remnant
List. You can go ahead and join the
Remnant List. You fill this out just
with some basic information. You will be
put onto a list.
And I send out information, and I will
eventually,
well, hopefully sooner than later,
be able to send out some more
newsletters and make it more
more professional and more interesting.
Um
I just really have not had time to do
much with it, but it's really is a goal
of mine. So, consider joining and get
notifications of live streams or videos
or other information. Okay, now this is
the biggest and latest
resource that I have provided on my
website, and this is the search of the
KJV word index as examples of what's
happening to our scriptures.
Now again, our Bibles in our own homes
are changing. These changes are
retroactive.
They are continuous. They are happening
in real time.
And it's unbelievable, but undeniable.
So, here is not a comprehensive list of
changes, okay?
But I have over 6,000
verses
available for you to look at that have
been changed.
Now, what I did is I am you should read
this, but I'm going to scroll down here.
You can look for new words, and then you
can click on these words to read the
verses. But you really can click on,
you know, um like the letter
I don't know what I should look at.
Maybe the letter U.
And you can look under the letter U, and
you can look for words that begin with
U, new words. Like, for example, we now
have the word unicorn in the Bible. And
God is now
being compared
to the strength of an unicorn in the
book of Numbers, Numbers 23:22.
Now, keep in mind
that even though I'm only highlighting
one word
in these verses, there can be a
multiplicity of changes in one verse
from grammar errors, nonsense verses,
new words, words omitted, whole new
doctrine.
But again, these are examples of new
words in the Bible. Now, some words I
have posted as new only because a word
has been multiplied, like the word
naked, okay? Naked has been multiplied
in scripture.
But anyway, so unicorn is now in the
Bible. Then continuing on, we even have
the new word unperfect. It's not even a
word in Psalms 139:16.
We even have the word us word now in the
Bible. That's right, us word is now in
the Bible three times. Never heard of
that word before in my life, but there
it is. But there are other words that
are more disturbing, if you will. Like,
for example, I'm going to go ahead and
show you. Um
we have and we have funny words. Like,
did you know that a bank is in the in
the Bible for money? That's right, we
have a bank
in the Bible now.
And not to mention, we even have bakers
in the Bible. That's right, we have
bakers and we have butlers in the Bible.
We even have bacon in the oven in the
Bible now. How crazy is that? We even
have the word bake meats in the Bible.
That's a new word that I never even
heard of before.
We also have backbone is now in the
Bible. And I just go on and on and share
changes with you, okay? Like, another
one that comes to my mind is let's go to
letter M. Magnifical is a new word in
the Bible. I never even knew it was a
word until the Bible changes. We even
have the word manchild is in the Bible.
I've never heard of the manchild until
the woke virus, okay? Until the Bible
changes.
But we're seeing all types of agendas
being imposed
into scripture today to prepare the way
for the Antichrist. We see a transgender
agenda, a homosexual agenda, an Islamic
agenda, a Mormon agenda, a Catholic
agenda, a new age agenda,
and on and on it goes. The Bible is
being prepared to worship the beast.
There is zero doubt in my mind.
He who reads, let him understand. Do you
understand?
It is the abomination of desolation
standing in the holy place, and it's
time to wake up in Jesus' name. Anyway,
so this is just a resource for you. You
can search by scripture verse, by word.
You can search by a book in the Bible to
see what's going on here, and so forth.
I'm going to go ahead and clear this.
And I'm also going to show you a couple
other things. Let me think of words that
I want to show you. The word pilots is
another new word in the Bible, pilots.
So, I'm going to click here, and you can
see the two verses with pilots in it.
And there you have pilots now in the
Bible. We have the word um
Um there's so many of them. Like, um
starting with uh let's see here. We have
camels of furniture in the Bible. In
Genesis 31:34. There you go. Did you
even know that camels could have
furniture, let alone now being in the
Bible? It is in Genesis 31:34.
We even have the word um a cart is now
in the Bible. We have cart in the Bible
now nine times. That's right, a cart. We
even have castles in the Bible. We even
have cabins in the Bible.
In Jeremiah 37:16, cabins. Now, when you
go through these verses, a few things I
want you to note is you may see other
changes in one verse,
okay?
Um
these verses are like almost
unrecognizable as [clears throat] I'm
looking through them. We even have
damsels in the Bible.
And you really need to read these. Read
these scripture verses
and ask the Holy Spirit to show you,
okay?
Because the changes are absolutely
insane,
absolutely ridiculous, and absolutely
self-evident. And it's time to wake up
in Jesus name. Did you know that we even
have I've got to show this to you. We
even have the word doctor in the Bible.
That's right. Doctor like a physician is
now in the Bible three times.
And we have Jesus now in the book of
Luke no longer sitting in the temple or
teaching in the temple. Let me put it
that way when he was a little boy. Do
you remember when he did that? Because
now the Bible is teaching that Jesus
when he was a little boy was in no
longer the synagogue, but he was in the
temple. And he was now he's now sitting
in the midst of doctors both hearing
them and asking them questions.
Absolutely not. Jesus was teaching
before the religious leaders and he was
speaking with authority and everyone was
amazed.
Don't you remember that? I remember
that. But now we have doctors in the
Bible. And on and on it goes. We have
lawyers in the Bible. We have um
we have sheriffs in the Bible. We have
deputies in the Bible. We have
physicians in the Bible.
We have um
other new professions are now dropped
into scripture.
And then we have God being depicted in
ways that are absolutely
horrendous.
It's time to wake up in Jesus name.
Please wake up. Please pray and fast and
search out the matter because the
changes
are obviously meant to
deceive.
And in fact, that's exactly what's
happening.
This is the strong delusion. These are
lying signs and wonders. And those who
do not discern what's happening are
underneath the strong delusion. And I
don't know about you, but I do not want
to be underneath the strong delusion.
It's time to wake up in Jesus name.
Please search out the matter. Spend time
researching this. It's going to be one
of the most important things that you
could do in this hour is to be alert and
to be sober.
Now when you look at these verses,
you're going to see all types of crazy
new words.
It goes on and on, okay?
We have palace now in the Bible
81 times in the King James Bible and
these are examples
of this.
All right, everybody.
That's what I wanted to share with you.
Um it's not perfect, but it is a
resource for you and I'd love to hear
your comments and let me know how you
use this. May God bless you. May God
protect you.
And may God's grace be abundantly
supplied to you.
Be strong and courageous.
Do not fear. Be dismayed, for the Lord
your God is with you wherever you go.
God bless you.